

Vladimir Yeresko

E-mail: vyeresko@gmail.com Phone: +380663233836

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Self-motivated with passion to learn I always look for a challenging and requiring deep immersion tasks. Working with them I search for the best solution by breaking down the problem into its main constituents and as a result by going through each of them I find the most optimized solution in terms of cost and time.

I started my path in gamedev when I was 17. I was searching around the internet for something to read about programming and stumbled upon a book about how to develop games in Adobe Flash. Since then it has appeared as one of the first item in my list of hobbies. i.e. game development, not development in Flash (it is old).

For many years I have been obtaining a lot of experience and knowledge in software development especially related to gamedev branch via self-learning, working as a freelancer and in a company as a member of an international game development team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Upwork

Feb 2016 — Sep 2016

Unity developer

- Create mobile games from scratch
- Optimize and make changes for existing solutions

Nordcurrent, Warsaw

Oct 2016 — Jun 2019

Game programmer

- Create gameplay prototypes
- Create and manage game servers
- CPU/GPU optimization
- Algorithms design

Ubisoft, Kyiv

Sep 2019 — Aug 2020

C++ Programmer

- Optimization and bug fixing
- Working on UI

Blackwood

Nov 2020 — Present

Gameplay Programmer

- Bug fixing
- New gameplay features implementation

SKILL SET

- Cross-Platform Development
- Unity, UE4, CryEngine
- C++, C#, Java, JS, Lua, Go, Bash
- Git, P4
- Math, Physics, Computer Graphics
- MySQL, Redis, CMake
- Analytical and creative thinking

Vladimir Yeresko

• Writing documentation

EDUCATION Secondary Education

Sep 2002 — May 2014

Gymnasia №71, Zaporizhia

Higher Education

Oct 2014 — Jun 2019

PJATK (Polish-Japanese Academy of Information Technology), Warsaw

INTERESTS

- Develop/Play video games
- Science, Philosophy
- Music
- Martial arts
- Comedy

REFERENCES

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/vladimir-yeresko-69296418a/

Vladimir Yeresko 2